<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE phrases SYSTEM "entities.dtd">
<epp:phrases xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:epp="http://eprints.org/ep3/phrase" xmlns:epc="http://eprints.org/ep3/control">


  <epp:phrase id="Plugin/Screen/User/DepositStatement:title">Deposit Agreement</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="Plugin/Screen/User/DepositStatement:update:button">Continue</epp:phrase>

<!-- New (virtual) field added to EPrint -->
  <epp:phrase id="eprint_fieldname_deposit_statement">Deposit Agreement</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="eprint_fieldhelp_deposit_statement">Before adding information about your thesis, you have to agree that we are allowed to store the information provided</epp:phrase>

  <epp:phrase id="metapage_title_user_deposit_agreement">Deposit Agreement</epp:phrase>

<!-- New fields added to users -->
  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldname_last_login">Last logged in</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldhelp_last_login" />

  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldname_privacy_statement">Privacy Agreement</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldhelp_privacy_statement">To use this system, you need to read and agree to the Privacy Agreement</epp:phrase>

  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldname_deposit_statement:intro">New rules relating to how we collect and process data - the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) - came into effect in the UK on 25th May 2018.<br />
Before adding your thesis to <epc:phrase ref="archive_name" /> you need to read and agree to the Deposit Agreement.</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldname_deposit_statement">Deposit Agreement</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldhelp_deposit_statement">Before entering details of your thesis you need to read and agree to the Deposit Agreement</epp:phrase>

  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldname_agreed_statements">Data Agreements</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldhelp_agreed_statements">To use this system, you need to read and agree to the Privacy Agreement</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldname_agreed_statements_agreement">Agreement</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldname_agreed_statements_time">When agreement was accepted</epp:phrase>


<!-- New fields added to requests -->
  <epp:phrase id="request_fieldname_privacy_statement">Privacy Agreement</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="request_fieldhelp_privacy_statement">To use this system, you need to read and agree to the Privacy Agreement</epp:phrase>

<!-- user_agreements namedset -->
  <epp:phrase id="user_agreements_typename_data_privacy_v1">Data Privacy Statement (v1)</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_agreements_typename_data_privacy_v1:full_statement">
    <p><strong>THIS IS AN EXAMPLE USER DATA PRIVACY STATEMENT. Please edit with your policies!</strong></p>
    <h2>Data Privacy Statement (May 2018; v1)</h2>
    <p>In creating this account you agree to the personal data you supply being stored in the United Kingdom 
and maintained by <epc:phrase ref="archive_name" />, through University of Leeds IT Service, on behalf of White Rose Libraries 
and the Universities of Leeds, Sheffield and York. This data may be accessed by colleagues from across 
these three institutions if necessary e.g. to offer support or resolve an issue. The data, including your 
institutional affiliation, will also be used to better understand the use and effectiveness of the 
service and identify areas for improvement. Individuals will not be identifiable from any generated 
outputs. These uses come under the following lawful basis under the General Data Protection Regulation 
(GDPR) 2018:</p>

    <blockquote><p> 6 (1) (e) - Processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the 
public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller.</p></blockquote>

    <p>Should you use your account to deposit your thesis/your research we will retain your personal data 
for the duration of our curation of this thesis/content.</p>

    <p>Should you not use your account to deposit content, the account will remain live for 12 months from 
last recorded activity. After this period, the account, along with any personal data it contains, will 
be deleted.</p>

    <p>The Universities recognise the importance of personal privacy and ensure that all personal data is 
held in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018. Compliance is managed by 
Data Protection colleagues across the sites, and the Data Controller for White Rose operations is the 
University of York, on behalf of the Universities of Leeds, Sheffield and York. </p>

    <p>Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you have a right of access to your data, a right to 
rectification, erasure (in certain circumstances), restriction, objection or portability (in certain 
circumstances). You also have a right to withdraw consent. If you would like to exercise these rights, 
or if you have any concerns or questions relating to Data Protection, please contact:</p>

    <p>*** ADD YOUR GDPR CONTACT DETAILS IN HERE!</p>

    <p>If you are unhappy with the way in which the University of York has handled your personal information 
you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office. For information on reporting a 
concern to the Information Commissioner’s Office, see <a href="http://www.ico.org.uk/concerns" target="_blank">www.ico.org.uk/concerns</a>.</p>

    <p>If you consent to your data being used and stored in this way, please tick the box to confirm, 
and continue creating your account.</p>
  </epp:phrase>

<!--  
  <epp:phrase id="user_agreements_typename_data_privacy_v2">Data Privacy Statement (v2)</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_agreements_typename_data_privacy_v2:full_statement">The full DP v2 statement</epp:phrase>
-->

  <epp:phrase id="user_agreements_typename_deposit_v1">Deposit Agreement (v1)</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_agreements_typename_deposit_v1:full_statement">
    <p><strong>THIS IS AN EXAMPLE DEPOSIT PRIVACY STATEMENT. Please edit with your policies!</strong></p>
    <h2>Deposit Statement (May 2018; v1)</h2>

    <p>In using this account to deposit your thesis, you agree to the personal data you supply being 
stored in the United Kingdom and maintained by <epc:phrase ref="archive_name" />, through University
of Leeds IT Service, on behalf of White Rose Libraries and the Universities of Leeds, Sheffield and York.
This data may be accessed by colleagues from across these three institutions if necessary e.g. to offer 
support or resolve an issue. The data, including your institutional affiliation, will also be used to 
better understand the use and effectiveness of the service and identify areas for improvement. 
Individuals will not be identifiable from any generated outputs. These uses come under the following 
lawful basis under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018:</p>

    <blockquote><p>6 (1) (e) - Processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the 
public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller.</p></blockquote>

    <p>The data will be retained for the duration of our curation of your thesis.</p>

    <p>Depositing your thesis with <epc:phrase ref="archive_name" /> adds it to a national - and 
international - network of open access online databases which promote access to research outputs so that 
they can be found, read, cited and built upon. Theses available in <epc:phrase ref="archive_name" /> will 
be available to all. Potential readers will be able to find your thesis through an ordinary search engine 
such as Google but also through other specialist, academic search engines, maximising the impact and 
profile of your research.</p>

    <p>Some of the data you share will be used to create the record page for your thesis, in accordance
with any limitations you set as part of the deposit process. This will not include your email address or 
any direct contact details. Staff from White Rose Libraries, Leeds IT Service, and the Universities of 
Leeds, Sheffield and York may use these details to contact you about your thesis. If your thesis is 
embargoed, requests for access during the embargo period will be sent to the email address you supply as 
the &quot;contact email&quot; for the thesis. White Rose Libraries will not share your contact details 
with the requestor.</p>

    <p>The Universities recognise the importance of personal privacy and ensure that all personal data 
is held in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018. Compliance is managed by 
Data Protection colleagues across the sites, and the Data Controller for White Rose Libraries operations 
is the University of York, on behalf of the Universities of Leeds, Sheffield and York.</p>

    <p>Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you have a right of access to your data, a right to 
rectification, erasure (in certain circumstances), restriction, objection or portability (in certain 
circumstances). You also have a right to withdraw consent. If you would like to exercise these rights, 
or if you have any concerns or questions relating to Data Protection, please contact:</p>

    <p>*** ADD YOUR GDPR CONTACT DETAILS IN HERE!</p>
 
    <p>If you are unhappy with the way in which the University of York has handled your personal information 
you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office. For information on reporting a 
concern to the Information Commissioner’s Office, see 
<a href="http://www.ico.org.uk/concerns" target="_blank">www.ico.org.uk/concerns</a>.</p>

    <p>If you consent to your data being used and stored in this way, please tick the box to confirm, and 
continue depositing your thesis.</p>

    <p>Please note that the responsibility for gathering appropriate permissions relating to any personal 
data held within your thesis, including relating to deposit in this repository, lie with you as the 
researcher. You must ensure any such permissions are in place to the satisfaction of your University 
before depositing your thesis.</p>
  </epp:phrase>

  <epp:phrase id="user_agreements_typename_request_privacy_v1">'Request a Copy' Privacy Statement (v1)</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="user_agreements_typename_request_privacy_v1:full_statement">
    <p><strong>THIS IS AN EXAMPLE REQUEST PRIVACY STATEMENT. Please edit with your policies!</strong></p>
    <h1>'Request a Copy' Privacy Statement (May 2020; v1)</h1>
    <p>As this content is currently not publically available you need to request access, either from the author or 
      other specified contact with the authority to grant access to this item.</p>

    <h2>How do we use your data and who do we share it with?</h2>
    <p>To allow them to consider your access request fully, we need to provide the author or other specified contact 
      with your details, including the reason you are requesting access and your contact details to enable them to respond.</p>
    <p>Your data may be also be accessed by colleagues from White Rose Libraries and the Universities of Leeds, Sheffield 
      and York if necessary e.g. to offer support or resolve an issue.</p>
    <p>The data will also be used to better understand the use and effectiveness of the service and identify areas for 
      improvement. Individuals will not be identifiable from any generated outputs.</p>

    <h2>How long will we keep your data?</h2>
    <p><epc:phrase ref="archive_name" /> will retain the details you submit in your request as part of our records 
      concerning the restricted content we curate. We will retain this data until the requested item is made publicly 
      available, or for 12 months (whichever is the longer period).</p>

    <h2>How do we store your data?</h2>
    <p>This data will be stored in the United Kingdom and maintained by <epc:phrase ref="archive_name" /></p> 

    <p>In placing this request you understand that:</p>
    <ol>
      <li>the personal data you supply will be passed to the author or specified contact for this content to enable them to 
        consider and respond to your request</li>
      <li>the personal data you supply will be stored and maintained by <epc:phrase ref="archive_name" /> as described above.</li>
    </ol>

    <h2>What is our legal basis for processing your data?</h2>
    <p>Data gathered as part of the 'Request a Copy' service will be processed under article 6 (1) (b) of the GDPR, i.e. to allow 
      us to perform a contract with you or take steps at your request, to enter into a contract.</p>

    <p>The Universities recognise the importance of personal privacy and ensure that all personal data is held in accordance with 
      the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018. Compliance is managed by Data Protection colleagues across the sites, 
      and the Data Controller for White Rose operations is the University of York, on behalf of the Universities of Leeds, 
      Sheffield and York.</p>

    <h2>What rights do you have in relation to your data?</h2>
    <p>Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you have a right of access to your data, a right to rectification, erasure 
      (in certain circumstances), restriction, objection or portability (in certain circumstances). You also have a right to 
      withdraw consent.</p>

    <h2>Questions or Concerns</h2>
    <p>If you would like to exercise the above rights, or if you have any concerns or questions relating to Data Protection, please contact:<br />
      *** ADD YOUR GDPR CONTACT DETAILS IN HERE!</p>

    <h2>Right to complain</h2>
    <p>If you are unhappy with the way in which the University of York has handled your personal information you have the right to complain
      to the Information Commissioner’s Office. For information on reporting a concern to the Information Commissioner’s Office, see www.ico.org.uk/concerns.</p>

    <p>If you consent to your data being used and stored in this way, please tick the box to confirm, then complete and submit your request.</p>
  </epp:phrase>

  <epp:phrase id="agree_to_statement">I have read and agree to the <epc:pin name="user_agreement" /></epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="agreed_statements_render_li"><epc:pin name="user_agreement" /> (agreed at: <epc:pin name="time" />).</epp:phrase>

  <epp:phrase id="user_fieldname_agreed_privacy_statement">Privacy Agreement</epp:phrase>

  <epp:phrase id="Plugin/InputForm/Component/Field/AgreeToStatement:open_modal">View</epp:phrase>
  <epp:phrase id="Plugin/InputForm/Component/Field/AgreeToStatement:close_modal">Close</epp:phrase>
  <!-- <epp:phrase id="Plugin/InputForm/Component/Field/AgreeToStatement:intro"><p>GDPR registration statement intro</p></epp:phrase>-->
  <epp:phrase id="Plugin/InputForm/Component/Field/AgreeToStatement:style"><style>
.agree-statement-title { font-size: 1.4em; font-weight:bold; }
.agree-statement-intro {}
.agree-statement-field {}
.agree-statement-input {}
.agree-statement-input.disabled { color: grey;}

.ep_form_action_button:disabled,
{
  border: 1px solid #999999;
  background-color: #cccccc;
  color: #666666;
}

button[disabled]:active, button[disabled],
input[type="button"][disabled]:active,
input[type="button"][disabled],
input[type="submit"][disabled]:active,
input[type="submit"][disabled] ,
button[disabled]:hover,
input[type="button"][disabled]:hover,
input[type="submit"][disabled]:hover
{
  border: 2px outset ButtonFace;
  color: GrayText;
  cursor: inherit;
  background-color: #ddd;
  background: #ddd;
}
.jqmodal {
  top: 50px;
  max-width: 1000px;
}
.jqmodal blockquote {
  font-size: inherit;
}

</style></epp:phrase>

</epp:phrases>
